sexgamesfree.net 2007-08-23

# Sex Game's Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy For SexGamesFree.net**  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate SexGamesFree.net's commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. **Personal Information**  
Any personal information that you provide to SexGamesFree.net shall stay absolutely safe, private and secure. We **DO NOT** share or resell personal information to outside sources. **Information Logged**  
SexGamesFree.net **DOES NOT** log any information about you, your computer, your internet service provider or your internet connection. **Cookies**  
SexGamesFree.net may use cookies to store information about your visits. This information can limited to merely tracking geographic, aggregate data and is not personally identifiable. However, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, advertisers may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser. **Third Party Advertising**  
SexGamesFree.net works with Advertisers that serve ads to this site. **External Links/Resources**  
SexGamesFree.net contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Even though we do try to link with the highest quality sites, we simply cannot guarantee the content meets our standards. **Contacting Us**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can [contact us.](http://www.sexgamesfree.net/contact/)
